BRIAN IGANA

BACHELOR OF ARTS

Contact: +2547 27288 048

Email: brianigana@gmail.com

RIURU, KIAMBU

PROFILE

I am a friendly person with good listening and communication skills. I have experience in interacting with clients as an Office Administrator, participated in public speaking events on Community Development and successful small-scale sales. I can quickly learn and adopt new skills required to accomplish desired objectives.

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

Microsoft Office Suite HTML, CSS, Vanilla JS Planning and Organization Skills

Sales Skills Basic MySQL Team Work

EDUCATION

Moi University 2017 - 2022

Bachelor of Arts in Political Science and Public Administration Second Class Honors (Upper Division)

Senende Boy's High School

2013 - 2016

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education B- (Minus)

Mkwakwani Primary School

2004 - 2012

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education C + (Plus)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Office Administrator (Volunteer)

15/8/2022- 12/2/2023

Office of the Governor, Ukunda Ward, County Government of Kwale.

- Provided clerical support to the office by emailing, copying, filling out documents and maintenance of office cleanliness;
- Led other volunteers on clients services and management of students' inventory list and preparation of bursary payment list;
- Strengthened communication skills through regular interactions with clients and the office team; and
- Worked flexible hours across nights and weekends to meet needed results.

Office Administrator (Industrial Attachment)

22/6/2021-21/9/2021

Office of the Governor, Ukunda Ward, County Government of Kwale.

- Resolved issues through active listening and open-ended questioning, forwarding major problems to the Ward Administrator;
- Monitoring and evaluation of community group projects;
- Actively participated in community sensitisation on development;
- Prepared minutes and monthly reports for the Ward Administrator.

Office of the Governor, Ukunda Ward, County Government of Kwale.

- Receiving clients;
- Prepared internal memo for office supplies;
- · Actively participated in public participation programs; and
- Prepared minutes for the Ward administrator.

HOBBIES

• Swahili creative writing.

REFEREES

AZIZ SALIM VUMBI,

WARD ADMINISTRATOR - UKUNDA WARD COUNTY GOVERNMENT OF KWALE. CONTACT 0722 666 912

WENANI KILONGI,

MOI UNIVERSITY - LECTURER, INDUSTRIAL ATTACHMENT ASSESSOR, CONTACT 0722 635690

MWANARUSI SAID,

VILLAGE ADMINISTRATOR - KILOLAPWA VILLAGE, COUNTY GOVERNMENT OF KWALE, CONTACT 0710 466 643